

ABOUT ME

I'm a left-brain/right-brain hybrid type and a self-taught user experience designer with 10 years of experience in professional and freelance graphic design. I'm passionate about the potential to improve not only healthcare and patient experience, but all aspects of life when people need help the most.

SKILLS

DESIGN SKILLS

User research, heuristic analysis, solution design (personas, storyboards, sketching, user journeys,), information architecture, content strategy, wireframing, UI design, illustration, prototyping, user testing, print design, web design.

DEVELOPMENT SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jquery, SCSS, Github, Bootstrap, Bourbon

SOFTWARE/TOOLSETS

Sketch, Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign, XD, Invision, Mail Chimp

OTHER SKILLS

Product strategy, excellent communication skills, experienced in stakeholder management, compelling presentation design & delivery, long-form & micro copywriting

KAT TOW

UX & DIGITAL DESIGNER

2921 N. Downer Ave, Milwaukee, WI (+1) 608 931 4465 kattow88@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Mar 2017 - present Digital Designer 2-STORY CREATIVE

RESPONSIBILITIES:

- Analyzed demographic data for preliminary user personas
- Completed baseline assessments
- · Designed digital assets
- Coded front-end for various projects.

July 2014 - Mar 2017 Marketing & Design Director

RENAISSANCE THEATERWORKS

RESPONSIBILITIES:

- Managed content and design of website
- Designed all season artwork, marketing, outreach, and fundraising materials
- Operated marketing, communications, audience development, & sales
- Coordinated content, design, printing, & mailing of company print & email communications

ACCOMPLISHMENTS:

- Increased single ticket sales by 40% over two years.
- Redesigned the company's website, allowing visitors to purchase subscriptions and tickets online, download photos, watch video, & access key information more easily.
- Overhauled the company's visual style for brand adherence, clarity, consistency, and relevance.

EDUCATION

Sep 2007 - June 2011 Lawrence University DESIGN FOR THEATER, GENDER STUDIES Capstones in scenic design, construction, & painting for THE TEMPEST

Sep 2016 - present

edX Coursera

*indicates coursework for University of Michigan MicroMasters in UX Research & Design

COMPLETED COURSE LIST:

Human-Centered Design: an Introduction; User Experience: Research & Prototyping; Introduction to User Experience*; Principles of Designing for Humans*; Evaluating Designs with Users*; UX Design: From Concept to Wireframe*

CURRENT COURSES:

Acumen+ IDEO.org: Design Thinking; Design in Healthcare: Using Patient Journey Mapping